Mid-journey, stable diffusion, DALL-E, and others are able to generate an image, sometimes a beautiful image, given only a prompt.
Midjourney，Stable Diffusion、DALL-E等这类产品，
能够仅通过一个提示（Prompt）生成图像，甚至有时生成的图像非常漂亮。
You may have heard of a vague description of these algorithms learning to subtract noise to generate an image,
你可能听过这些算法学会减去噪声来生成图像的模糊描述，
but in this short course, Sharon will step you through a concrete implementation of image generation using a diffusion model
在这个短期课程中，Sharon将带领你了解
使用扩散模型进行图像生成的具体实现，
so that you understand the technical details of exactly how it works.
这样你就能明白它究竟是如何工作的。
Cool, thanks Andrew.
太酷了，谢谢Andrew。
In this course, you'll be learning about the current state and capabilities of diffusion models used today.
在这门课程中，你将了解到目前扩散模型的现状和能力。
You'll start by understanding the sampling process, starting with pure noise and progressively refining it to obtain a final nice-looking image.
你将从了解采样过程开始，从纯噪声开始，
逐步优化，最终获得一个好看的图像。
You'll build the necessary programming skills to train a diffusion model effectively.
你将学会训练扩散模型所需的编程技能。
You'll add context to the model so that you can control what you want it to generate.
你将为模型添加上下文，以便你可以控制想要生成的内容。
And finally, by implementing advanced algorithms, you'll learn how to accelerate the sampling process by a factor of 10.
最后，通过实现先进的算法，你将学会如何将采样过程加速10倍。
This is an intermediate to advanced course.
这是一个中级到高级的课程。
We assume you're familiar with Python and basic neural network training.
我们假设你熟悉Python和基本的神经网络训练。
So for example, we'll assume you know what backpropagation is.
所以举个例子，我们会假设你知道
什么是反向传播（Backpropagation）。
We'll use PyTorch throughout.
我们将在整个过程中使用PyTorch。
But if you're familiar with other machine learning frameworks, such as TensorFlow, you should be able to follow along just fine.
但是，如果你熟悉其他机器学习框架，
如TensorFlow，你应该也能跟上进度。
And so the running example we'll use for this short course will be generating 16 by 16 sprites, like those little 8-bit characters used in video games.
我们在这个短期课程中使用的实例将是生成16x16的像素精灵，
就像那些用在视频游戏中小小的像素角色。
We chose this example so that it's feasible for you to not just go through the notebooks,
我们选择这个例子是为了让你不仅能浏览 Notebook，
but also run them yourself to generate cute sprites yourself right there in that Jupyter Notebook.
还能亲自动手运行它们，
以便在 Jupyter Notebook 中生成可爱的像素精灵。
For example, generating molecules for drug discovery.
比如，生成用于药物发现的分子。
So when you understand the technical details of diffusion models,
所以，当你理解扩散模型的技术细节时，
you'll also be in a better position to understand and perhaps apply such models yourself.
你也会更好地理解并可能自己应用这些模型。
Many people worked together to build this short course.
很多人共同努力创建了这个短期课程。
I want to thank Aaron Lou and Mehmet Giray Ogut for their significant contributions.
我要感谢Aaron Lou和Mehmet Giray Ogut的重要贡献。
And on the DeepLearning.ai site, also Geoff Ladwig and Eddy Shyu.
还有在DeepLearning.ai网站上的
Geoff Ladwig和Eddy Shyu。
So with that, let me hand it over to Sharon, and I hope you enjoy the course.
那么，让我把剩下的时间交给Sharon，希望你能喜欢这门课程。
Great.
太好了。
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。